welcome to the AI native Dev podcast
hosted by Guy Pani hello and myself
Simon Maple hello if you're a developer
or a Dev leader join us as we explore
and help shape the future of software
development in the AI era we'll explore
new and exciting AI Parts Dev Tools in
conversations with their makers covering
both how they work and how you should
use them we'll also discuss the role of
a software developer and where it's
headed lastly we'll try to uncover what
the future of software development looks
like what we call AI native software
vment now every Tuesday I'll be talking
with Trailblazers to bring you insights
into the latest AI tools and best
practices keeping you up to date with
The Cutting Edge advancements in the
industry and every other week I'll speak
with experts and leaders to Deep dive
into what AI native software development
will look like talk about what value it
would bring and how you should prepare
for it today and we'll also be having a
monthly Roundup where guy and myself
will be sharing our learnings and try to
connect today's reality with our
aspirations for tomorrow yeah and maybe
a little bit of banter always always
banter so Tune In And subscribe to
supercharge your development today and
be part of the next generation of
software development